But, but, but...
What are you doing?
Can you please stop playing with me?
In a chair in the dressing room.
Can I ask you to come out?
Go on!
This is not recess.
All is well
With the double official.
I'll be talked into a lot of things.
Nice to meet you, sir.
You switched well. That was a deep apology.
Now, it's time for the "Suddenly Explorers", we have Mr. Uchitani and Mr. Yasumori here with us today.
We've had them move around a lot, but today's video doesn't have a lot of movement.
Did you want to move?
Maiken gymnastics is fine.
Shikon Fuguna
I'd like to make an announcement right away.
Today's exploration is about making and decorating Gunpla!
I just said let's make and decorate Gunpla.
I'm sure you've heard of Gunpla before, right?
Of course!
Have you ever made one?
Gundam Planet, right?
No, not like Chocolate Planet.
Gundam Planet.
Gunpla...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Gundam plastic models.
Is that so?
Yes.
Gundam plastic models? Gundam plastic models? Yes, yes, yes, there's no other way.
Today, we're going to build a Gundam model of Oakstar on the fifth floor of Evin's, and we'll work together to have it decorated as we like.
I know it's your first time... but please give it your best shot.
Let's go!
Okay, here we go.
This is the Gunpla we're going to make today.Gunpla.
We'll put it on over here.
There's no such thing.
It's not so easy.
Why not?
It wasn't that kind of scene.
It's not a sexy scene.
It's not a wow.
This is a Gundam.
None of the three of us know much about Gundams.
I don't know the name of it at all, but I've seen it... of course... the coolest Amuro Rei, like the first one.
the upper half is Yasumori-san and the lower half is Fujitani-san the right half is Yasumori-san, I don't know
Let's do it while assigning them to each other
Wow, what shall we do?
I wonder if I can do this...
I imagine it's full of smaller parts.
I'm not sure if I can do it... but there are a lot more detailed parts than I imagined.
How do you do that?
I'm not sure how to do this... but it looks like the mouth is bent and the liquor's been detected.
I'm sure there are special nippers for this, too.
What are we going to do?
I'm sure you'll be able to find it.
So it's easier to separate them here, right?
I think it's easier to separate them here.
It's like the top and the bottom.
Let's run it and sort it... this one's red.
It says "a 1" at the top, so we should just cut it down.
That's right... we should break it down here, right?
I've never seen any Gundam.
But the Gundam in Odaiba... yes... yes... that's the one in Diver City, isn't it?
I don't even know if I'm taking the right pictures.
It's okay, it's okay. I'm just a beginner.
I'm scared!
What was that? You're scaring me!
You're waving a pretty girl around, aren't you?
Easy, easy, easy!
She's reacting like someone who just used nippers for the first time. Reacting like someone using nippers for the first time
No, it's almost the first time.
Nasumori, you have an image of dexterity. You've been one of the most dexterous explorers so far.
Yes, with a sense of style.
I was rather strong in arts and crafts.
I majored in either art or music in high school, but I majored in art for three years.
Not music? You like it.
You have taste.
I used to do calligraphy.
You're good at it. You're not so good at making things by hand, are you, Ms. Fujitani?
If I had some wood and was allowed to put it together, I'd be good at it.
But I don't really dislike this kind of quiet work.
I like to concentrate on something.
Here it comes! Here it comes! I think it's a girl's shoe, like an elementary schooler's.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
My feet are cramped! My feet are cramped!
Who are you talking to? No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, not me. Oh, my God, I think I brought something.
Did you give it back to Folter? Yeah, that's not good.
This is amazing. Impressive.
I'm impressed. - Okay, guest O, guest X.
Who's there? Is Eiichiro here?
Anyone familiar with Eiichiro?
You don't talk like a doctor... about airplanes.
This is it. Thank you very much for your help.
Eichinoju, are you there?
Eiino10, are you there?
Eiino10, this way please.
E-2-10, this way, please.
What receptionist? Here.
The body's finished.
You're early.
Where are you going next?
Head and face.
That was quick.
Wow! Oh, my gosh! Here it comes! Today's work! That's great!
It's here, it's here, it's here! He was putting it all together without hesitation! It's almost done! Can the joints of the legs move?
Yes, they do! Oh, my gosh! So energetic!It's moving! Oh, my gosh! So energetic!
Hey! My knee was hurting so much! It's so wide!
I can move my joints!
It's done!
Can you see it?
My face is like a Gundam all at once!
That's amazing! It's so detailed!
It was so detailed!
I love detail work.
Really?
That was great! That's great! You're good!
It came to life!
This is how they know you're serious. Are you sure you don't want them to know that too?
I don't want to be exposed. - That's not what I'm saying, is it? But you've both done it.
You're lying? No, they haven't found out yet? No, I can't! We're still alive!
We're still alive! We're still alive! Do we have a globe? There's a globe around here.
That's it? Look!
Do it! Do it! We can still make it! Do it!
Look at it! Take a look! Take a look before you say "still alive"!
It's starting to look gorgeous! Gundam face!
Don't mess with it!
Combined!
Shield! Shield!
Oh! Gundam!
Now, let's have the ceremony!
Sacred!
Scary! Scary, scary, scary!
Ha!
It's done!
Good work!
All up!
This is Hanatama!
Did it take you 30 minutes?
I think it took less than 30 minutes.
What do you mean?
Movement and poses.
You're moving, aren't you?
Great, great, great, great.great, great, great!
I like it.
It's very childish, and it's like turning it into a douche.
Hands up!
What?
Gundam, why don't you say, "Hands up!
I thought you said he was a robber.
I'm the righteous one.
I'm sorry, sir.
Nice!
Great!
I'm gonna go now.
I'm off!
When I leave the house, I'm going to do this Gundam thing.
I think I'm going to make this into a Komadori and dance the Torokko choreography or something.
It's like a pose or something.
Vertical.
Ah! Inaba.
What's that? What is this? Yasumoto.
What's this? It's a bridge. I do gymnastics. It's a skill I showed at the auditions.
I can play bridge! Bridge on my feet... on Gundam Planet.
It's a bit complicated. Gundam Planet's RX78 income.
I don't know how to read it. Entry grade. I don't know what it is.
It's an audition. Entry grade. I can play bridge.
May I see that? Bridge, then.
Here we go.
Yes! Wow!
Have you been playing bridge since you were a little girl?
You can come back when you talk.
You're funny. Thank you.
Is he all right? It looked like you took your hand off. Your shoulder.
Shoulder? Is that your skill too? Yes, it's true. The joints are soft.
It was removed from a soft spot. I'll let you know the result later.
Yes, I understand. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Actually, please text me on the walkie-talkie.
It's too cool! Wait a minute! It's too unique!
No, it's a game with unlimited imagination.
Was it easy?Was it easy?
Once I got the hang of it, it was easy... at first... when I opened it, I was like, "Wow, that's a lot of work." But yes.
You were okay with it too, Mr. Futchitai? Yes, it was fun.
You had a fine head. You were concentrating on it.
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
I think I did my best.
But the real work starts here.
Play and decorate.
We're good at that.
I'd like to do some decorating.
To some extent. Thank you for providing us with the bare minimum of materials.
Let's name this Gundam.
This Gundam, even though it's a Gundam...
Kira Kira Gundam Taro.
Kira Kira Gundam Taro
What should we call him? This is long.
Kira Taro.
Kira Taro is good.
That's good.
Yes, I like it.
Then let's make him into KIRATARO.
He's waiting for me now.
KIRATARO, too.
I want to decorate this.
Very nice.
Okay, weapons...
Oh, shields.
I got it.
I want to decorate weapons.
Weapons! Weapons!
I know you're nervous because it's your first time.
Of course.
Are you okay? Are you nervous? Does it hurt?
I don't know what's going to happen.
You're tilting your head a little. He's tilting his head a little.
I don't know what's going to happen to me.
Is that what he sounds like?
He's tilting his head.
He's nodding his head.
He's saying, "What's going to happen to me?
I gave this story on purpose.
Check it out with the love scene.
She's doing her idol thing.
Oh, she's dancing.
Oh, man, this is gonna be so much fun.
Who's that? Who are you?
Petals are falling. Love is flowing.
They're coming for you.
Side dish?
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They're sticking together.
Yeah, it is.
Why is it like there's electricity in it?
Peek-a-boo!
There's Pikachu!
It's decorated like this.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
It's so cute!
It totally changes the atmosphere.
Pretty all at once.
It's nice.
It's so cute!
What's going on back there?
It looks like this.
It looks like a birthday outfit.
It's a good idea... a Gundam birthday party!
I like it.
Very girly!
She's good!
I bet the manicurists and such are really good! I'm sure you're a good manicurist or something.
What's the matter with you?
Your reaction is a little weird.
It's not a horror movie.
It's a horror movie, isn't it?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just saw Home Alone.
You're too influenced.
It's funny, isn't it?
It's finished... it's finished... the front... the one and only...
The one and only Deco Gundam. And the legs are done by two people.
Two people did the legs... and two people did the last one.
I'll hesitate...
Fujitani... how cute are the ribbons?
It's wings... and with these ribbons, it can fly.
Like a fairy, she's got a gun right here, with glitter on the end of the muzzle.
And there's glitter on the end of the muzzle, too, so when you get shot with it, you get all sparkly and pretty and sparkly and pretty and pretty.
The opponent will fall in love with the Melfendang dam!
Yay! It's done!
It's so cute!
Yay! I did my best!
So, I've successfully completed it! I really did it in less than an hour, even though I'm a Gundam beginner, and I was able to make it this far in less than an hour.
I can make the only one and only Gundam in the world for myself, so please try to make one too!
I'd like to have it displayed somewhere, maybe by hmv, but as soon as it's decided, I'll put it in the summary section of the video.
I'll put a message in the video as soon as I decide on a name for it.
Kira Taro, please come and watch it.
That's all for now.
And now, for the first time...